Listen, here's something you'll want to know.
It exists. A way back to Japan.
Long ago, we Four Major Human Errors
tried to destroy the world,
but only for one reason.
Because we wanted to return to our home world.
There really is a way to get back, you know.
I don't care about that!
Here in this world, I have Menou!
I don't want to go home at all! Ever!
Maa, maa. How lovely.
I almost wish I could watch that
friendship on the big screen.
I think that line does a good enough
job as trailer material.
Bye now!
I prefer to go home without watching the credits,
so feel free to do what you want.
I-I think it's bad manners not to stay
seated until the lights come up!
Ah, yes. Of course.
Being able to have this kind of
conversation is probably really fun!
What happened to Menou?!
Okay, time to begin one final struggle.
Ready...
Action!
Episode 12
The Duo's Journey
Invoke
[Gale]
It shouldn't be long before the
fog captures Pandemonium.
Then if we hold out until then, we win.
Still, that thing is a pain to deal with.
But it only has as many lives as the
number of people sacrificed to it!
Etheric Connect-Scripture,
3:1-Invoke
[And the oncoming enemy did
hear the toll of the bell.]
If we keep cutting it down, its lives will eventually run out!
Maa!
But before that, your lives might run out first, you know.
If it's a matter of brute strength, I shan't lose!
Maa! What a powerful blow!
Oh no! The scattered limbs are heading into town!
I guess I walked right into that one.
Your Highness, please go! I'll deal with things here!
I'll take you up on that.
Now it's just you! How awful!
It seems like connecting to the
earthen vein recharged your ether a bit.
What a weird body you have.
Not as weird as yours!
Still, I definitely don't have ether to spare.
I'm not sure if I can hold her off
until the fog swallows her up.
Menou...
She'll probably yell at me...
But even so...
I want to protect Menou!
Maa!
Look, everyone!
The nice lady's going to play with you again.
How's that?
The same attack over and over
again will bore the audience, right?
My scripture!
You're so strong with that thing.
I want to see you be more desperate!
Now what are you going to do, Miss?!
That expression! That's right, that's what I want!
Try harder!
Don't give up!
Or you'll get ripped to shreds!
Maa?!
That's...
Use it!
Miss Priestess!
You owe me one!
Princess Ashuna!
All I need is this fist of mine!
I thank you for letting me use this, Your Highness!
Invoke
[Flameburst]
This drains more ether than I thought...
Maa, maa.
I don't think you're suited for that weapon, Miss.
I won't last much longer!
Is that it, Miss?
I thought you might entertain me a bit more,
but you were more ordinary than I thought.
This ends with you dead!
Is that it, Miss?
I thought you might entertain me a bit more,
but you were more...
Maa, and I told her not to come. How nasty of her!
Menou!
Akari!
Please, Menou! Use me!
Maa, you think you're the heroine?!
You won't get away!
Maa.
I guess I don't have much time left.
Why did you come?!
Because...
...I don't want to let you die, Menou.
That's why...
I want you to use my ether!
Okay.
Your power... let me use it!
Yes!
Promise me you won't lose!
Of course not!
After all, I'm a pure, just, and strong priestess!
Maa, what a beautiful friendship.
But no. What I want is a horribly dark ending!
That was easier than I thought.
Ma-?!
That's the one that swallowed the dagger earlier!
Akari, here we go.
Okay.
Menou, I'll give you everything I've got!
Maa...
I'm happy I got to connect with Menou,
but maybe it was a mistake
for this version of me to come.
Good luck explaining this one, other me.
Akari.
You did great.
Maa...
Pandemonium.
You're already out of the lives sacrificed for you.
Isn't that right?
And you can't sacrifice your own body
to resurrect yourself anymore, either.
That's right.
I separated more than half of my flesh from the real me.
I went for giant size over invulnerability.
To have fun doing this movie.
What are you really after?
Do you want revenge on the world for imprisoning you?
Maa, how completely wrong.
I was just enjoying the process. I have no objective.
I thought Human Errors are supposed to
have lost all memories and personalities.
How could you think messing up the world is "fun"?
That's because I'm Chaos.
I exist in this world to kill and to bring
chaos in accordance with this planet.
In the name of the Pure Concept attached to this body,
I interfere with all that is good.
So, Miss...
I'll tell you something you want to know.
The sword of certain destruction once wielded by Ivory,
the Sword of Salt...
That has the power to destroy any Pure Concept.
Even that girl who governs Time.
Are you happy? Or not so much?
Doesn't it make your heart uneasy?
That's right.
After all, my Chaos seeps in and poisons your very soul.
This time it's actually over, eh?
Very impressive. To think you destroyed that thing.
No, it was all thanks to Your Highness's sword.
But that was merely a pinky finger.
True. And there are usually two pinky fingers in all.
I very much doubt this is the end.
By the way, that girl is an otherworlder, isn't she?
I remember seeing her.
Perhaps she's the reason why Pandemonium
managed to escape the fog?
I would very much like to talk to her...
about all kinds of things.
But I'm rather exhausted at the moment.
I'll turn a blind eye, just for today.
Give my regards to Momo.
...I'm alive?
Good morning! I'm so glad you're awake!
Am I... in hell?
No, no. It's the real world. How do you feel?
Just awful.
I feel like someone twisted a dagger into my head,
followed by my body exploding from inside.
What is this?
I see!
Then the people I used as material must
have died some pretty horrible deaths.
"Material"?
Then did you bring me back to life?
Yup!
I used the dead bodies buried here
to reconstruct some missing parts.
One of the bodies belonged to an otherworlder,
and that made for great magecraft material.
Oh... I see...
Why would she help me...?
Manon, you actually have an older sister, you know.
A bright, active girl who's full of energy...
She loved singing and dancing.
But more than anything, she loved movies.
Even when the memories fade
and your personality is gone,
perhaps something remains intact.
What's this about?
Oh, just something that ended ages ago.
First a thousand, then ten years ago.
Hey, I'm thinking of doing a movie on a larger scale next!
You'll help me, won't you?
Sure.
Let's bring even more chaos into this world...
...you and me, together.
I'm impressed, Momo.
Pastor Sicilia was amazed how quickly you recovered.
It's all thanks to you worrying about me, Menou.
Your love is the best medicine I could ever get!
Right, right. I do hope that's true.
Momo?
Um, Menou. I'm so sorry.
You had a horrible time all because I messed up...
I'm the one to blame.
I relied on you too much when I didn't
have enough information on the enemy.
That's not true! I-!
Don't get too excited.
You're still recovering.
R-right...
So was it the Sword of Salt...
that the Human Error suggested?
Yes.
Apparently it can destroy any Pure Concept.
Do you think that's reliable?
I don't know.
But it didn't sound like a lie.
Isn't the Sword of Salt near the Sanctuary,
in the far west?
On the continent of salt.
I went there once with the Master, a long time ago.
I'm going to go there again.
I'll use the Sword of Salt to kill Akari.
So that she doesn't become an
atrocity the way Pandemonium did...
Momo, will you come along like you've been doing,
without revealing yourself to Akari?
Yes.
Of course I can do that...
Thank you so much.
Not only for tending to Momo,
but for the compensation as well.
It's fine.
I hate to think how much more damage
there might have been without you.
Though it's still more than I would prefer to handle.
I'm sure you'll bring peace back to
the city in no time, Pastor Sicilia.
Are you trying to make up for what your Master said?
Not at all. I truly mean it.
Well then, if you'll excuse me...
Ms. Menou.
One last thing. This may be unnecessary...
But you're different from Flare.
You should follow your own path,
no matter what kind of path it may be.
If, hypothetically,
I could guarantee that Akari would never kill anyone,
harm anything,
or let her Pure Concept go out of control...
What would I do then?
I'm back.
Menou!
Akari?
What's the matter?
Because... I woke up and you were gone,
and I thought you might have left me behind...
Of course not!
I just went to the church to talk with Pastor Sicilia.
Akari, are you asleep?
No.
I just want to confirm something.
You really don't remember anything?
From halfway through the evening ball to
when you woke up after the battle?
Th-that's right.
I really have no idea.
I see.
Both when I rescued her and when
she came during the battle,
Akari was clearly conscious.
But it doesn't look like she's lying.
I don't think Akari's the type who's
good at hiding things, either.
Menou.
I don't remember, but I worried you, didn't I?
I won't ever do that again. I'm really sorry.
So please, don't hate me.
You're so silly.
I wouldn't hate you for something like that.
After all, you're my-
"You're my" what?
Hey, what were you going to say?
Hey! Come on!
This is your one chance to say it! Right now!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Uh... my source of stress on the journey...?
MENOU!!
You can't, Menou.
The Menou I love,
the one who's a valiant Executioner,
can't do that.
If you act for her sake,
I just know those feelings will eat away at you.
That's why...
I'll do it instead... and kill her myself.
Once again, we're setting off for the Sanctuary,
huh Menou?
That's right. You'd better be ready for this, Akari.
It's not going to be an easy journey.
Aye-aye, sir!
I'll be fine as long as we're together, Menou!
That's right, as long as we're together.
If, hypothetically,
I could guarantee that Akari would never let her
Pure Concept go out of control, I would...
No, that's not for me to think about.
Before Akari loses all of her memories or sense of self,
I swear I'll kill her.
After all, I'm a pure, just, and strong villain!
Hey, let's take the first step together again!
Oh, all right. Sure.
Okay, here we go.
Ready, and...
Menou, no matter what stands in your way,
make sure you kill me.
And make sure you survive.
I'll do anything to ensure that happens.
Star
The Starkhusk
Four Major Human Errors
Dragon
The Sword of Salt
Vessel
The Material Room
Chaos
The Pandemonium
So not only Chaos,
but a portion of Vessel has also escaped...
Etheric World Connect
(Conditions: Met) - Scripture,
Third Charter-Invoke
[Our world is beyond words.]
This is the first time even a fragment has
emerged since the Starhusk hatched.
It was worth the insufferable number
of repetitions we've gone through.
Now then, time to get going...
...to kill my apprentice for the zillionth time.